New York State Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO, Environmental Conservation Division (PEF/ENCON); Records apap114
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Executive Board, 1978-2000; 3; 3.9 cubic ft.
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1991 December 12-1991 December 13 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 29)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, Ethics Grievances, 1991 December 12-1991 December 13 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 30)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1992 March 2-1992 March 3 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 31)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1992 March 2-1992 March 3 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 32)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, Ethics Grievances, 1992 March 2-1992 March 3 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 33)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, Operations Department Quarterly Report, 1992 March 2-1992 March 3 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 34)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1992 May 14-1992 May 15 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 1)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, CHANGE-NY Information, 1992 May 14-1992 May 15 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 2)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, Operations Department Quarterly Report, 1992 May 14-1992 May 15 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 3)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1992 July 27-1992 July 28 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 4)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1992 July 27-1992 July 28 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 5)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1992 December 3-1992 December 4 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 6)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1993 February 25-1993 February 26 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 7)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1993 February 25-1993 February 26 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 8)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1993 May 3-1993 May 4 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 9)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1993 July 29-1993 July 30; 1993 September 27 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 10-11)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1993 December 2-1993 December 3 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 12)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1994 February 17-1994 February 18 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 13)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1994 February 17-1994 February 18 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 14)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1994 May 5-1994 May 6 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 15)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1994 May 5-1994 May 6 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 16)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1994 August 4-1994 August 5 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 17)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1994 August 4-1994 August 5 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 18)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1994 December 1-1994 December 2 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 19)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1994 December 1-1994 December 2 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 20)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1995 March 2-1995 March 3 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 21)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1995 March 2-1995 March 3 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 22)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1995 May 25-1995 May 26 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 23)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, Ethics Grievances, 1995 May 25-1995 May 26 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 24)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, Ethics Grievances, 1995 May 25-1995 May 26 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 25)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1995 August 3 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 26)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1995 December 8 (Box 3 (3-Executive Board), Folder 27)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1996 March 7-1996 March 8 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 1)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1996 March 7-1996 March 8 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 2)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1996 May 31 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 3)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1996 August 22-1996 August 23 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 4)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1996 August 22-1996 August 23 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 5)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1996 December 4 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 6)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, Ethics Grievances, 1996 December 4 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 7)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1997 March 5-1997 March 6 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 8)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1997 May 29 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 9)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1998 December 2 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 10)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1999 March 3-1999 March 4 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 11)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1999 June 9 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 12)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1999 August 24-1999 August 25 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 13)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1999 August 24-1999 August 25 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 14)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1999 December 1 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 15)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 2000 March 1-2000 March 2 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 16)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 2000 March 1-2000 March 2 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 17)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 2000 May 17-2000 May 18 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 18)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 2000 May 17-2000 May 18 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 19)
  - Executive Board, Membership Lists, 1979; 1982; 1985-1986; 1991; Undated (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 20)
  - Executive Board, Miscellaneous Materials, 1979 January-1979 April (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 21)
  - Executive Board, Miscellaneous Materials, 1979 May-1979 July (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 22)
  - Executive Board, Negotiations Advisory Committee Meeting Kit, 1979 June 21 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 23)
  - Executive Board, New Member Orientation Kit, 1991 August 1 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 24)
  - Executive Board, Report on Resolutions of the First Annual Convention, 1980 February 20 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 25)
  - Executive Board, Reports, 1990 August; 1990 October; 1991 February; 1991 July (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 26)
  - Executive Board, SEIU Report on Anti-Inflation Program, 1978 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 27)
  - Executive Board, Special Meeting Kit, 1992 September 24 (Box 4 (3-Executive Board), Folder 28)
- Committees, Programs, and Events, 1975-2000; 4; 3.54 cubic ft.
  This series contains records of PEF committee activities at both the state and local level, along with information on a wide range of other programs and events. Particularly notable is coverage of PEF annual conventions from 1979-2000, although not all years are included; the statewide and regional Political Action Committees; the Women's Program; the statewide Health and Safety Committee; Leadership Development Conferences, and the Public Service Training Program.
  There is also significant coverage of conventions held by PEF's affiliates: the American Federation of Teachers (AFT), the New York State Union of Teachers (NYSUT), and the Services Employees International Union (SEIU).
  Also included are files on political parties and reform groups within PEF; most significantly, the Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union and the Pro-Member Party.
  Not included are committees, programs, and events connected to labor/management relations between Division 169 and the Department of Environmental Conservation or to the Executive Board. These are found in Series 2 and Series 3, respectively. Also not included are subject files on organizations with no direct PEF connection. These files are found in Series 1.
  - AFT Convention, Constitutional Amendments and Resolutions, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 1)
  - AFT Convention, Constitutional Amendments and Resolutions, 1986 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 2)
  - AFT Convention, Constitutional Amendments and Resolutions, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 3)
  - AFT Convention, Correspondence and Publications, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 4)
  - AFT Convention, Correspondence and Publications, 1986 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 5)
  - AFT Convention, Correspondence and Publications, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 6)
  - AFT Convention, Correspondence and Publications, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 7)
  - AFT Convention, Correspondence, Reports, Agendas, Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 8)
  - AFT Convention, Programs, 1984; 1986; 1988; 1990 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 9)
  - AFT Convention, Publications, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 10)
  - AFT Convention, Report, 1986 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 11)
  - AFT Convention, Report, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 12)
  - AFT Convention, Report, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 13)
  - AFT Convention, Resolutions, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 14)
  - AFT Convention, Resolutions, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 15)
  - AFT Convention, Roll Call of Delegates, 1984; 1986; 1988; 1990 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 16)
  - Albany PEF Coalition Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 17)
  - Black Caucus, 1984-1985; Undated (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 18)
  - Civil Service Committee, 1983-1987; 1991; 1995 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 19)
  - Civil Service Committee, Region 8, 1989 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 20)
  - Civil Service Council, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 21)
  - Committee Appointments, 1982; 1985-1987; 1989-1995; 1998-1999 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 22)
  - Community Service Award and Divisions Banquet, 1983-1985 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 23)
  - Community Services Program, 1985; 1987; 1988 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 24)
  - Constitution and By-Laws Committee, 1982 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 25)
  - Division 169 Audit Committee, 1985; 1988; 1990-1992 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 26)
  - Division 169 Program Committee, 1986-1989; 1991-1992; 1995-1996; 1998 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 27)
  - Division 202 Council, Undated (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 28)
  - Divisions Committee, Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 29)
  - Divisions Committee, Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 30)
  - Divisions Committee, Correspondence, 1988; 1990 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 31)
  - Divisions Committee, Minutes, 1984-1986 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 32)
  - Environmental Quality Committee, 1986 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 33)
  - Executive Council, Minutes, 1992-1996 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 34)
  - Health and Safety Committee, Statewide, 1980-1990 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 35)
  - Health and Safety Committee, Statewide, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 36)
  - Health and Safety Training Proposal, 1985 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 37)
  - Leadership Conference, Region 8, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 38)
  - Leadership Development Conference, Civil Service Law, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 39)
  - Leadership Development Conference, Discipline, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 40)
  - Leadership Development Conference, Fair Representation, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 41)
  - Leadership Development Conference, Grievance and Contract Language, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 42)
  - Leadership Development Conference, Negotiations, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 43)
  - Leadership Development Conference, Taylor Law, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 44)
  - Local and National Labor Marches, 1983; 1985 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 45)
  - Members United, 1999; Undated (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 46)
  - New York State PEF, 2nd Annual Convention, 1980 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 47)
  - New York State PEF, 3rd Annual Convention, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 48)
  - New York State PEF, 4th Annual Convention, 1982 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 49)
  - New York State PEF, 5th Annual Convention, 1983 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 50)
  - New York State PEF, 13th Annual Convention, Committee Reports and Legislative Agenda, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 51)
  - New York State PEF, 13th Annual Convention, Issues and Programs, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 52)
  - New York State PEF, 13th Annual Convention, Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 53)
  - New York State PEF, 13th Annual Convention, Program and Yearbook, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 54)
  - New York State PEF, 13th Annual Convention, Resolutions, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 55)
  - New York State PEF, 14th Annual Convention, Committee Reports, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 1)
  - New York State PEF, 14th Annual Convention, Correspondence and Publications, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 2)
  - New York State PEF, 14th Annual Convention, Proposed Amendments, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 3)
  - New York State PEF, 14th Annual Convention, Proposed Legislative Agenda, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 4)
  - New York State PEF, 14th Annual Convention, Resolutions, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 5)
  - New York State PEF, 15th Annual Convention, Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 6)
  - New York State PEF, 15th Annual Convention, Publications, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 7)
  - New York State PEF, 15th Annual Convention, Reports, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 8)
  - New York State PEF, 15th Annual Convention, Resolutions and Proposed Amendments, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 9)
  - New York State PEF, 17th Annual Convention, Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 10)
  - New York State PEF, 17th Annual Convention, Publications, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 11)
  - New York State PEF, 17th Annual Convention, Resolutions, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 12)
  - New York State PEF, 21st Annual Convention, Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 13)
  - New York State PEF, 21st Annual Convention, Publications, 1999 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 14)
  - New York State PEF, 21st Annual Convention, Resolutions and Proposed Amendments, 1999 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 15)
  - New York State PEF, 22nd Annual Convention, Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 16)
  - New York State PEF, 22nd Annual Convention, Publications, 2000 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 17)
  - New York State PEF, 22nd Annual Convention, Resolutions, 2000 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 18)
  - New York State PEF, Founding Convention, Summary, Undated (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 19)
  - Nominations/Elections Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 20)
  - NYSUT Convention, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 21)
  - NYSUT Convention, Correspondence and Publications, 1984 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 22)
  - NYSUT Convention Information, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 23)
  - NYSUT Convention, Representative Assembly, 1986 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 24)
  - NYSUT Convention Resolutions and Amendments, 1984 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 25)
  - Parking Committee, 1982-1991; 1999 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 26)
  - Political Action Committee, 1983 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 27)
  - Political Action Committee, 1984 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 28)
  - Political Action Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 29)
  - Political Action Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 30)
  - Political Action Committee, 1990-1994; Undated (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 31)
  - Political Action Committee, Legislative Conference and Lobby Day, 1986 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 32)
  - Political Action Committee, Legislative Report, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 33)
  - Political Action Committee, PAC Report, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 34)
  - Political Action Committee, Policy, 1980-1981; 1984; 1986 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 35)
  - Political Action Committee, Political Skills Training, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 36)
  - Political Action Committee, Region 8, 1983 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 37)
  - Political Action Committee, Region 8, 1984 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 38)
  - Political Action Committee, Region 8, 1985-1988; 1992; 1995-1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 39)
  - Pre-Retirement Seminar, 1987 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 40)
  - Professional Development and Quality of Working Life Committee, 1981-1986; 1988; Undated (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 41)
  - Professionals for PEF (Pro-PEF), 1982-1984 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 42)
  - Pro-Member Team, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 43)
  - Public Service Training Program, Agendas and Reports, 1984-1989 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 44)
  - Public Service Training Program, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 45)
  - Public Service Training Program, Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 46)
  - Public Service Training Program, Courses and Workshops, 1984-1986; Undated (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 47)
  - Public Service Training Program, General Information, 1984; 1990; Undated (Box 2 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 48)
  - Public Service Training Programs, Regional Liaisons, Undated (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 1)
  - Public Service Training Program, Surveys, 1985 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 2)
  - Realizing Employee Achievement and Productivity, Conference, 1987 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 3)
  - Regional Retreats, 1988; 1990; 1993 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 4)
  - Research Scientist Committee, Arthur Young Study Information, 1987 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 5)
  - Research Scientist Committee, Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1975; 1987-1990 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 6)
  - Research Scientist Committee, FOI Update, 1987 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 7)
  - Research Scientist Committee, Minutes and Agendas, 1985; 1987-1990 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 8)
  - Research Scientist Committee, Patent and Copyright Policy Issues, 1985; 1987 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 9)
  - Research Scientist Committee, Patent and Copyright Policy Issues, 1993; 1994; Undated (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 10)
  - Research Scientist Committee, Policies and Correspondence, 1983; 1985-1989; 1991 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 11)
  - Research Scientist Patent and Copyright Policies, 1990-1992 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 12)
  - Research Scientist Peer Review Panel, Correspondence, 1984-1985; 1987-1990; Undated (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 13)
  - Research Scientist Peer Review Procedures and Policies, 1987-1988; 1990; Undated (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 14)
  - Research Scientist Promotion Probationary Period, 1979; 1984-1985; 1987-1988; 1994 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 15)
  - Research Scientist Specialties, 1983; 1985; 1987-1988; Undated (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 16)
  - SEIU 75th Anniversary Convention, Committee on the Future Report #5, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 17)
  - SEIU 75th Anniversary Convention, Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 18)
  - SEIU 75th Anniversary Convention, Proposed Resolutions and Amendments, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 19)
  - SEIU 75th Anniversary Convention, Publications, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 20)
  - SEIU 75th Anniversary Convention, Report of the Officers, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 21)
  - SEIU 75th Anniversary Convention, Report to the Building Service Division, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 22)
  - SEIU 75th Anniversary Convention, Report to the Healthcare Division, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 23)
  - SEIU 75th Anniversary Convention, Report to the Office Worker Division, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 24)
  - SEIU 75th Anniversary Convention, Report to the Public Division, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 25)
  - SEIU Convention, Committee Reports, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 26)
  - SEIU Convention, Correspondence and Publications, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 27)
  - SEIU Convention, Program, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 28)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, 1980; 1982-1988; Undated (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 29)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Election Materials, 1985 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 30)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Election, News Clippings and Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 31)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Election, Press Releases, 1982 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 32)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Legal Issues with Executive Board, 1984 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 33)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Legal Issues with Executive Board, News Clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 34)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Meetings, 1982-1988; Undated (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 35)